Dilshad Alam COLLEGE STUDENT

Experience

ARTICLE WRITING

Quora (online platform) | October 2019 - Dec 2019

- Over 80.000+ content views.
- 1500+ daily average readers on my articles

SELF LEARNING

Udemy, online-learning.havard.edu| september 2019 - December 2019.

- Finished computer fundamentals course.
- Finished basics of web-developments.(Advanced HTML, advanced CSS and basics of javascript).
- Currently doing course named: The Complete Web Developer: Zero to Mastery(includes both front end and backend-uses react framework.

Education

BRINDAVAN COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING

Bangalore, India 2018 - present

- -1st sem with 91%
- -5th sem with 83%

MERIDIAN INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL

Kathmandu, Nepal | 2007 - 2017

- Grade 10 with 86%

Personal Information

Name: Dilshad Alam

Date of birth: 6th March 2003

Nationality: Nepalese. Hobbies: Reading,

cooking, sports, writing, online discussions. Languages: Maithili, Nepali, English, hindi and

urdu (written and spoken),

Personal Profile

I am a 16 years old student who loves to learn new things. I have completed various courses online on platform like udemy and I love to write articles online on Quora. My goal is to become a full-stack web-developer.

Contact Details

Phone Number: 81978 00369 dilshad.alam3215@gmail.com dilshad.alam3214@gmail.com

Achievements

- Full scholarship from 1st grade- 10th grade.
- Highest scorer (2018)- 91%
- Highest scorer (2019)- 83%
- Bronze medal(Under-16) in district level Table-Tennis tournament(Team Event).
- 4 gold medals in school-level tabletennis tournaments.

Skills

Table-tennis

• HTML5	1111
• CSS3	1111
 Javascript 	111
 Bootstrap 	111
 Article writing 	1111
 Video editing 	1111